# **Fahad Akhtar**

### Web Developer

Senior Web Developer with over 3 years of experience in the Backend area. In the past 1 year I have been heavily involved in Front-End development as well. Eager to face new challenges that will help me contribute to a great cause and learn more about UI/UX.



+92 3463521303

fahdshaykh@outlook.com

www.linkedin.com/in/fahad-akhtar-838560119/

### **Education**

#### **BS** Computer science

GCU Faisalabad - 06/2012 to 06/20216

- Making small games in JavaScript.
- Spend some time in studied programming books.
- Football is favorite game during study.

# **Experience**

RatedSolution - 06/2020 To Current

D.G.Khan, Pakistan

- Worked in a 10-person team of Local and American devs and designers.
- Pulled from PHP, SQL, JavaScript and other back-end library knowledge to bolster programming resources.
- Holding weekly meetings with clients to discuss their needs, aims and development progress.
- Developed, Designed, and Implemented Database structure, Storage structure, and Web service required for File/Content Management System.
- Modified existing code written in programming languages such as Laravel and JQuery.

**E-VisionSol** - 06/2018 to 05/2019

#### Multan, Pakistan

- Started as the junior web developer
- Frequently Scrum master of a 6 team of devs and designers.
- Developed many websites for difference types of business.
- Learned GitHub and project deployment.
- Manage different website.
- Built with new technology and ideas.

# **Strengths**

### Expression of Ideas:

As seen from my experience of talking to clients and giving them updates on their demands.

### > Collaboration:

Sharing new technology terms and clean code practicing. Collaborating with team members via Git and VS Code(live share).

### > Attention to detail:

F ocus on delivering work on my time. Work with my senior and junior team members and learn from them.

#### > Time management:

A ble to work on 2 to 3 projects at once while remaining calm and delivering quality end products.

### **Skills**

- Laravel
- CodeIgniter
- MYSQL
- Rest API
- Bootstrap
- JQuery
- Angular.js
- Vue.js

# Language

- English
- Urdu